[Music]
the year is 1887 sir John a McDonald the
Prime Minister of Canada establishes a
new insurance company the manufacturers
life insurance company created to make
lives better by protecting the financial
future of families across the country
ten years later in 1897 we expand into
Asia and soon begin operating in Myanmar
issuing our first insurance policy in
1903 we continue to protect families
futures in Myanmar until operations are
interrupted by World War two since those
early days we have continued to grow
into a global leader in the insurance
industry operating in over 20 countries
across the globe at the center of this
growth are our exceptional insurance
advisors the men and women who advise
customers making decisions easier and
lives better and as advisors help
Manulife grow
they also help their communities because
we invest in healthy lifestyles
and raise financial literacy through
education in Canada United States Japan
Singapore Indonesia Cambodia and across
the globe
we have driven social and economic
progress that continue to transform the
lives of millions now it's time for
manual life to support the families of
Myanmar and with Myanmar advisers as
part of our global team we're building a
prosperous future for me
[Music]
[Applause]
become a manual life insurance advisor
secure a better future
[Music]